Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jericka-henry (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Satisfaction Relationship Building Business Development

Certifications

Occupational Studies of Health and Science

Tech Sales Career Track

Honors-Awards
I Can African

Jericka Henry

BDR | SDR | SaaS| CRM | B2B New York City Metropolitan Area

Summary

Growing up in New York City brings out every natural gift that sleeps inside of you. I learned early on having effective communication skills is the key to building, learning and growing your brand (you). Tech Sales is definitely a place I can expand this skill. At Springboard I conducted effective qualification calls and implemented objection handling strategies. I also executed on critical tech sales fundamentals including pipeline development and prospect research and as a result I successfully passed over 20 course assessments to demonstrate understanding and delivery of impactful tech sales practices.

As a massage therapist for 5 years and 10+ years in the food hospitality industry, sales, communication, email marketing and client prospecting have been my tools I've used to build solid relationships and revenue.

While working as a sales representative selling headphones and electronics in the airport of Atlanta GA, it was there I found my love for storytelling and solution selling. I became the top three sellers in the district in warranties from February 2022 - May 2022 increasing monthly quotas by 3%.

I can't wait to share all of my different customer aqusitions and gifts with a company that is always learning new ways to grow.

Experience

Springboard

1 year 2 months

SDR/BDR Fellow at Springboard March 2023 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Effective Engagement strategies and communication

Conducted effective qualification calls and implemented objection handling strategies

Successfully passed over 20 course assessments to demonstrate understanding and delivery of impactful tech sales practices

Executed on critical tech sales fundamentals including pipeline development, researching qualified leads, prospect research, email marketing, cold calling and solution selling

Sales Development Representative March 2023 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Effective Engagement strategies and communication

Conducted effective qualification calls and implemented objection handling strategies

Successfully passed over 20 course assessments to demonstrate understanding and delivery of impactful tech sales practices

Executed on critical tech sales fundamentals including pipeline development, researching qualified leads, prospect research, email marketing, cold calling and solution selling

Marshall Retail Group/InMotion Salesperson January 2022 - May 2022 (5 months) Atlanta, Georgia, United States

With my knowledge of the products in the store, I helped customers purchase headphones, speakers and other tech accessories that fit their needs. Using other customers experiences through storytelling, has helped me up sell on products and warranties. I helped customers with end-to-end services, made payments using Posi, returns, exchanges and documented any damaged items. I opened the store, kept inventory and stocked the shelves.

Dr. Breines Chiropractic office Medical Massage Therapist January 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 3 months) Staten Island, New York, United States

Provided massages to clients with pre or post injuries, collected and documented S.O.A.P. notes, sanitized, restocked, and organized massage Page 2 of 3

rooms, completed clinical procedures and gathered patient data for interpretation by physician. Up-sell on longer duration of massages based on their emotional needs.

AIRE Ancient Baths Licensed Massage Therapist October 2014 - October 2016 (2 years 1 month) New York, New York, United States

Up-sell on services we offered. Performed Swedish, Deep-tissue and pre-natal massages, Prepared oil and lotions for massages. Listened to clients carefully to determine their end goal of the massage session.

Education

Springboard

Certification, Tech sales · (2022 - 2023)

Allies Place for Culinary Education
Certificate, Culinary Essentials/Knife Skills (25hrs) · (September 2022 - September 2022)

The Swedish Institute for Health and Science
Associate's degree, Massage Therapy/Therapeutic Massage · (September 2011 - October 2014)

Mercy College

Some College, Music Industry and Technology · (September 2008 - May 2010)

Activity

04/18/2024, Imeila Fonua added candidate to BDR- Test Sample